# **Bradley Orego**

User Experience Researcher. Entrepreneur. Dancer.

#### SUMMARY

9+ years experience working with companies from startup to Fortune 500.

Over 500 unmoderated remote research sessions with UserTesting, Validately, UserZoom, mTurk. Analytics tools include FullStory, Google Analytics, Mixpanel, and Heap. Statistical analysis using Excel, Python, SPSS.

# **HIGHLIGHTS**

# \$10M+ IoT R&D Usability Research

- Designed study, recruited participants, conducted 30+ sessions, and presented analysis & recommendations. \$2M+ saved in production costs.
- Presented report and findings to SVP of Marketing, SVP of Engineering.

### Fortune 500 Corporate Innovation

- Lead 6 months of generative research to guide product strategy, including ethnographic interviews, wizard-of-oz prototypes, and low-fi prototypes.
- Research and design for 10,000-user pilot program for insurance agents, including interviews, ethnographic research, and rapid prototyping.

# **EXPERIENCE**

1010data - Director of User Experience

2019 - Present

- Developing a scalable research process across all of 1010's products and departments, working closely with Customer Success, Sales, and Marketing.
- Lead 1010's UX Department and worked to unify design across all products.

**Prolific Interactive** - Senior User Researcher

2018 - 2019

- Served as the sole Researcher for all of SoulCycle's digital department.
- Facilitated Prolific's shift from UX Design to User Research, including updating service offering, department structure, and career progression.

#### American Family Insurance - Lead Designer

2016 - 2017

• Guided 4 product teams through research, ideation, testing, development, and launch. Assisted with vendor selection, due diligence, and acquisitions.

#### MobileIgniter - Product Lead

2014 - 2016

• Designed and ran 18 usability studies to support product development and client work. Worked directly with clients and lead 4-person tech team.

#### Nextt - UX Lead

2013 - 2014

• Injected per-sprint research into company's agile process. Improved conversion rate by 19% and onboarding completion by 46%.

#### Zebradog Studios - Digital Designer

2012 - 2013

Converted digital team from waterfall to agile, increasing velocity by 250%.

Brooklyn, NY (Remote OK) 716.939.1126 hello@bradorego.com https://bradorego.com

#### **SKILLS**

Usability Design, Usability Research, Heuristic Analysis, Survey Design, Focus Groups, Ethnographic Research, User Interviews, Expert Interviews, Card Sorting, Task Analysis, Personas, User Stories, Hallway/Guerilla Testing.

UI Design, UX Design, Mobile App Design, Product Design, Rapid Prototyping, Information Architecture, A/B Testing, Iterative Design, Service Design, Wireframing.

Agile, Scrum Master, Product Owner, Data-Driven, Backlog Prioritization, KPI/OKR, Reporting, Customer Segmentation, Competitive Analysis, Issue Management.

#### **TOOLS**

HTML, CSS, SCSS/Stylus, JavaScript, Angular, Vue.js, Ionic, Stencil.js, Node.js, Firebase, TensorFlow.js.

Sketch, Adobe Suite, Figma, InVision, UserTesting, Validately, UserZoom, mTurk, FullStory, Google Analytics, Mixpanel, Office Suite, Python, SPSS.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Rochester**

CLASS OF 2011

B.S. Computer Science (HCI)
B.A. Psychology
Minors in Spanish, Dance
Take 5 Scholar

**Epic Systems** - Software Developer, UI Liaison

2011 - 2012